<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Consulting | XLTech Solutions</title>
    <link>/tags/consulting/</link>
      <atom:link href="/tags/consulting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Consulting</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>©&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;2019&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;XLTech Solutions Pte Ltd</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:01 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/logo-640.png</url>
      <title>Consulting</title>
      <link>/tags/consulting/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIO-on-Call</title>
      <link>/solution/consult/cio-on-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:01 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/solution/consult/cio-on-call/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As your CIO-on-Call, XLTech provides senior management engagement on IT effectiveness, costs and strategic alignment, without the overhead from hiring a senior manager in a critical but non-core role.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We work with your staff to ensure IT skills, planning and delivery are thinking long-term and sustainability, and not floundering on fundamentals that distract value creation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTO-on-Call</title>
      <link>/solution/consult/cto-on-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:01 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/solution/consult/cto-on-call/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CTO-on-Call is designed for start-ups and businesses that require a technical oversight or consuling during the formative design and development stages of solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As your CTO-on-Call, XLTech can help you define, resolve and document your project’s architecture, design principles, integration solutions, interface specifications, API, RFP/RFQ process, technology stacks, data models and solution selection.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Foundations</title>
      <link>/solution/consult/project-foundations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:01 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/solution/consult/project-foundations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We can help you establish new project and programs from proposals, central office establishment, RFP/RFQ, planning and skilling needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clients new to technology projects, have had mixed results previously or prefer to ensure expertise review prior to engaging a large contracting firm, we help ensure your interests are prioritised.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Revitalise</title>
      <link>/solution/consult/project-revitalise/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:01 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/solution/consult/project-revitalise/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is designed for inflight projects and programs where independent review or audits are required. This can be limited to observation recommendations, or can be extended to cover re-alignment and delivery of the changes necessary to course correct the initiative.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
